The Amanda Seals Show.
Kaitlyn Clark.
Not surprisingly, WNBA first draft.
However, people are up in arms
because they don't feel like her contract
is equal with the male NBA players
despite her being the number one draft pick to the WNBA.
So she's going to earn $338,056
over the course of four years.
The last year's number one NBA draft,
are you ready for what they got?
$55 million.
Damn.
Given the NBA's substantial revenue
and its current subsidy of the WNBA,
I believe there should be incentives
to explore additional funding avenues
to narrow the wage gap.
So for example,
every time Draymond Green gets fouled out of a game,
the NBA should have to send a million over to the WNBA.
Every time?
Every time.
That'll close the pay gap by 20%.
Every time LeBron flops on a play,
and fakes being hurt another milli or two,
sugar ladies.
Yeah, I think that's fine.
Every time John Morant gets caught with that bang,
yeah, man.
Not the Blakey.
Mo' money, mo' money, mo' money.
Black people should care because over 70% of the WNBA is black.
Yes.
We over there.
We are, we are, we are.